Do you think Florence is the kind of person
who will just let others step on her?
Do you think that Florence
is the type of person
who will not fight back
if someone is trying to oppress her?
If there's one person who can fight back,
that's Florence.
That's bad.
How is the view from the floor?
Hey!
You already saw that I fell
and now you're asking me
to hold on to your drink?
We were minding our own business
and then she suddenly meddles.
She's not aware of her place here.
She labeled us as if we were
the villains in her life.
Well, if that's what she believes,
then I guess we should play the part.
I heard a rumor that
there's this secret sorority
of popular girls on campus.
They are known by the name Aylip.
Aylip?
They're a very powerful group.
And, based on my sources,
there's someone new
that they're declaring persona-non-grata
on the first day of school.
I saw a girl who looks exactly
like you the other day.
I don't believe in what they say
"leap of blood" but...
I felt something.
Is she my grandchild?
Is Celestina alive?
I'll just use the CR.
This is off-limits.
Why?
I said this is off-limits.
Did you do that on purpose?
If you don't want to be hit,
find a different place,
not here where we are playing.
Don't! Who are you?
Let go of me! What's with you?
Do you often hang out here?
I like their iced tea.
Troy.
Wait, Babe.
Do I know you?
Have you seen Florence?
Florence is missing?
Who are you? What do you need from me?
Let me go, please.
What's with you? Who are you?
Tristan?
Aldus?
What are you doing? You fools!
We have no choice.
You are in big trouble, Florence.
Me, trouble?
Why?
That's my picture.
How did they get that?
TWPS? What's written there?
The West Philippine Sea?
No, The Worst Person in School.
It means, you have offended
an influential girl in school.
That's why now,
you're the target enemy of everyone.
What did you do?
The most important question now is,
why are you sweet to me all of a sudden?
I'm touched by your concern for me.
I knew it, you two are kind-hearted too.
Didn't you hear what we told you?
You're the target enemy #1 of Aylip
and they have a lot of members
here in the school.
So you have a big problem.
I heard what you said.
Do you think I'm not scared?
But what can I do? Hide in a hole?
What do you want me to do, drop out from GU?
Mope in one corner,
forget all my dreams because
those Aylips don't like me?
They're mad at me and
now I'm target #1 enemy?
It's like this.
I saw a student they were bullying earlier
and I meddled.
Maybe that's why they're picking on me.
Do you know my father's favorite saying?
The way to the heart of a man or woman
is through their stomach.
What?
- She's kidding.
- What are you talking about?
But I don't think that applies to you guys
because it seems like your tummy
and intestines are not good.
It looks like there's a blockage
going to your heart as well.
So what's more applicable to you is
"the only thing necessary
for the triumph of evil
is for good men to do nothing."
And with cases like this
that you're bullying someone
and there's a witness like me
when we won't do anything and be quiet...
Wait, did you kidnap me just to tell me this?
You could've texted me.
This is more fun.
Be thankful it's just this.
- Is that so?
- You should've seen your face.
You fools!
- You're really...
- Just a little push
and you were about to cry.
But seriously, what's your plan?
Your life here won't be easy,
especially since you've offended
one of the influential groups
here in school.
Well, I will do what I can do,
and that is to fight
and not give up the fight.
I was able to survive the Ferells,
what more of them?
Well then, good luck.
Yes, you need a lot of luck.
Hey, where are you going?
Can't you take this off?
Fun, fun. What's so funny?
Spotlight. You're an expert in kidnapping.
Let's go our separate ways, Florence.
Don't come too close.
You're on your own
and we've warned you already.
I thought you were really concerned about me.
The Aylip is powerful
and the girls might stay away from us
once they find out that we know you.
I agree. And if you need help, don't call us.
Call Owen and Troy.
Or Nero.
Bye. Let's go.
I don't think they'll come here.
Hopefully, they won't be here.
There's no one here.
Nero?
So, this is the perfect meeting place
for both of us?
I knew it, I'd find you here.
Did you receive my messages?
Message?
What message?
I didn't get any message from you.
No texts or calls, not even an email.
You used to send me cute little messages
using messenger birds.
So those messages weren't for me?
But even that...
I haven't received anything from you.
You haven't spoken to me since last year.
It's like you just suddenly disappeared.
I'm sorry.
Just stop pretending like
you've been sending me messages,
because the truth is...
you just suddenly disappeared.
Nero, I just want to talk to you...
to settle things once and for all.
I can't keep doing this,
just figuring things out by myself.
It's just better if we move on.
Sometimes I feel like you're no longer
the Nero that I've known before.
And if we stay in this relationship,
the more I'd get hurt
and the more we'll hurt each other.
I agree.
You're right.
It'll be better for both of us.
Why did you assume too much, Florence?
Do you really believe that Nero
will send you...
Florence.
I've been looking for you
for quite a while now.
Are you okay?
Why do you look that way?
Did someone hurt you?
Have you heard about Aylip?
Tristan and Aldus talked to me already.
You have to be careful, Florence.
We don't know what's going on in their minds.
You know it'll be better
if you ride with us going home.
I can even accompany you here in school.
Owen, I promise,
you don't have to worry about me.
I want to be alone first.
I can handle myself.
Florence!
Hey, wait! What's with you?
Yes, Troy?
If you're here to tell me that
the group Aylip has declared me as TWPS,
I know that already.
And I already know that all people here
are watching my every move,
that's all of them.
But thank you for your concern
but I'm not scared.
And for your information,
I'm not intimidated,
and the more I'm not terrified of them.
But you know, I've realized,
they're starting to make trouble.
Well then, I'll end it.
What did she say?
I even ran, and that's tiring.
You, you, you, you, and all of you.
Are you the reason why the sorority, Aylip,
is picking on me?
What's your problem?
Is there nothing you can do with your lives?
Are you bored?
Do you think I'm scared of you?
And you...
Will you really let them step on you?
What's with you? Have you gone crazy?
And for both of you,
what satisfaction are you getting
from stepping on someone else?
Because I came here to learn,
to make myself whole,
and achieve my dreams for my family.
How about you?
I think you came here to belittle others.
What kind of person are you?
How did your parents raise you?
What's your class right now?
See you at the dean's office.
Deserve.
(Loser.)
What's with you, Florence?
It's your first day of classes
and you've been called
to the dean's office right away.
You're really a failure.
You'll even destroy a bench.
What's with you, Florencia?
You're such a failure.
Are you okay?
Don't let one bad day discourage you.
Trust me, tomorrow will be much better.
Hi, I'm Antonia.
And if we stay in this relationship,
the more I'd get hurt
and the more we'll hurt each other.
I agree.
You're right.
This will be better for both of us.
Florence. Florence Dela Cruz at your service.
And so that you won't forget,
give me an F, give me an L,
give me an...
Just Florence.
Wow, you really seem like a fun person.
Is that why you're here in the dean's office?
Did you have too much fun?
Huh?
I'm sorry, I was just trying
to cheer you up...
but it seems my sense of humor failed.
No.
Actually, the reason why I'm here is
that I had too much anger.
I lost my mind
and did a lot of barking in the library
a while ago,
that's why the librarian sent me here
for disciplinary action.
Wow, you really weren't kidding.
You must have been very upset
to forget to keep quiet in the library.
Well, that happens if you find out
that the messages from the doves
are not for you.
Excuse me?
I mean, how about you? Why are you here?
Well, I'm actually here
because I want to talk to the dean.
Since last year I was the top student,
I was highly recommended
by the fundamental chairs and faculty staff
to be this year's
head of the university's student body.
Wow, really?
That's exciting.
Well, it isn't something I look forward to,
to be honest.
Aside from the heavy work,
being the head of
the students here in Gyronella
comes with tremendous pressure.
Imagine, everyone who has gone
through this position
ended up with very successful careers.
Senators, supreme court justices,
cabinet secretaries, CEOs.
How about Ms. Universe?
None yet.
But I can definitely be the first.
That made me nervous.
I was just joking.
I'm just making you laugh.
Thank you.
No worries.
Anyway, you're not the only one
having a bad day.
You? Bad day?
You're already having a bad day
with that beauty?
What if it's a good day?
You'll be more beautiful.
Well, the difference is...
I kind of expected that this day is coming.
Huh?
Why?
What happened?
Well, I... I have...
I just ended things with my boyfriend.
Are the kids home?
They're in their rooms now.
Owen and Aldus, Tristan and Troy.
I don't think they'll eat, Sir,
because they ate in school.
Nero on the other hand
is still in the school library.
He's finishing something,
according to Dencio.
How about Florence?
Oh well, she sent me a message.
She said, she was just fixing something.
I pity Florence.
She needs to wake up early to cook for us.
And now with the added pressure of school,
maybe she might not be able to
handle the pressures of life.
Trust me, Don Ferell,
Florence doesn't feel that way.
Maybe she's energized
because of her opportunities now.
Truthfully, a heart with big dreams
doesn't easily get pressured or get tired.
Yes, but let's help her
to achieve her dreams...
since our agreement is
she'll cook for the kids.
Now that they're back to school,
she doesn't have to wake up early.
But how about you, Don Ferell?
You like her home cooking so much.
True.
I guess I'll just have to
settle with your cooking.
Don Ferell, don't belittle my cooking skills.
After all, I wouldn't have won Dencio's heart
if not for my cooking.
Well, try to win my heart with your cooking.
Let's see.
Challenge accepted, Sir.
Anytime.
See, I told you.
The dean is easy to talk to.
Thank you for backing me up
with the dean earlier.
Don't mention it.
You know, being noisy in the library
is actually a minor offense.
Just don't do it again.
It was really nice meeting you, by the way.
Nice meeting you too, Antonia.
Anyway, it's getting late.
Do you have a ride?
Yes, maybe it's waiting for me
around the corner.
Okay, I'll go ahead.
I'll see you around.
Thanks again for what you did earlier.
I'll see you around Antonia.
I'll go here. There's a way here.
You're the target enemy #1 of Aylip.
And they have a lot of members here in school
so you have a big problem.
Why are you following me?
Show yourself.
Do you think I'm scared of you?
Who are you?
Why are you following me?
I came from the library when I saw you.
What do you need?
I already called Mr. Dencio.
Just ride home with us.
I'll take the trike home.
There are no more tricycles.
I'm sure there are a lot of tricycles
on the highway.
I'll wait there.
Don't you want to take just one vehicle?
That's less pollution.
Do you know what's less pollution?
That's to walk home,
the best way to defeat global warming,
zero carbon emissions.
Are you sure?
It's dark there.
Okay, I'll go with you.
Where's Nero?
Here, I'm texting him.
Where is he?
Don't tell me
it's just the first day of school
and he acted like a good student.
Nero is Grandpa's standard
when it comes to school.
That's why we're pressured.
He said he's on his way home.
And Florence is with him.
They're together?
After the incident,
the dean talked to her,
that's why she stayed in school till late.
Good thing they saw each other.
Why, Bro, is there a problem?
What's his problem?
I don't know.
To be honest, I don't want to ask.
Just like a story, the plot thickens.
Maybe it's his first day.
Heavy flow.
So, Nero, how's your first day of school?
Are you okay?
I'm just okay.
How about you?
I'm okay too.
How come you don't look convinced?
From what I heard,
it looks like you had a bad day at school.
So what?
What? Will you lecture me too?
What's with the Ferells?
Do you guys really want to protect me?
What's this, Messianic complex,
or all of you can't help
but be a Prince Charming?
Do you all want to save a damsel in distress?
And with my situation,
I am a damsel in distress.
You know, Nero, for your information,
I am not your damsel in distress.
I am my own woman.
I don't need men to save me
because whatever fate throws at me,
I can face that by myself.
It's not bad to ask for help from others,
and it's not good
that you always keep everything to yourself.
Don't talk as if you're not hurting
or act like you're not having a hard time.
Because no matter how you hide
what you're feeling,
I'm sure sometimes your heart
is asking for an ally.
It's not a weakness to ask for help.
Sometimes, that's the way things are.
We need others so we can bounce back.
Sometimes, be true to what you're feeling.
Don't be scared to show it to others.
Wow!
Wow.
Be true?
Really?
It's not bad to ask for help from others,
and it's not good
that you always keep everything to yourself.
Don't talk as if you're not hurting
or act like you're not having a hard time.
Because no matter how you hide
what you're feeling,
I'm sure sometimes,
your heart is asking for an ally.
It's not a weakness to ask for help.
Sometimes, that's the way things are.
We need others so we can bounce back.
Sometimes, be true to what you're feeling.
Don't be scared to show it to others.
He talks as if he's someone high and mighty.
Do you need anything?
Yes, there's something I need.
You said that we should be true to ourselves.
Well, then I'll be true too.
You're so thick-faced.
It's not bad to ask for help from others,
and it's not good
that you always keep everything to yourself.
Don't talk as if
you're not having a hard time,
or act as if you're not hurting.
Because no matter how you hide
what you're feeling,
I'm sure sometimes,
your heart is asking for an ally.
It's not a weakness to ask for help.
Sometimes, that's the way things are.
We need others so we can bounce back.
Wow, you talk as if your heart is wide open.
Do you think you're not keeping
all your problems to yourself?
Hey, Nero Sebastian Araneta Ferell,
you have no right to tell me that
because you're actually doing that
to hide what you truly feel.
See, why can't you be true now?
Your heart is crushed to pieces, right?
Because the woman you want
officially broke off with you.
I was there earlier.
It's just better if we move on.
Sometimes I feel like
you're not the same person that I know.
If we stay in this relationship,
the more I'll get hurt,
and the more we'll hurt each other.
I was also in the garden earlier.
I heard everything
you talked about with Antonia.
And what's bad is
you thought that everything was okay
because you thought
she received all your messages
using the doves.
And what hurts the most,
I am the stupid one who thought
that I'm the one you were
sending your sweet messages to.
Look, I didn't mean to hear
your conversation with Antonia.
What you're saying is true,
I was acting tough like I'm not scared.
That's why I'm staying away
from Camille and Aira
because I'm avoiding them from the start.
That's why I went to the garden
because I was hiding from them.
But when I realized
that your conversation with Antonia
is so private and personal,
I left already, okay?
I'm sorry
but ever since I burned down your bat cave,
I never intended to invade your privacy.
That's just an accident.
But it's a good thing that happened
so I'd find out that the letters
from the dove weren't for me.
I just want to make up
for all the kindness you did for me,
and I know you made effort to cheer me up.
So I can feel good about myself.
Now I get it...
when you told me that I was nice to you.
So my pets end up with you.
Why didn't you tell me right away?
Some people are having a hard time
showing their true feelings.
That's why sometimes,
some guys resort to secret messages.
And what I can advice you is...
not to confront him.
Give him time and eventually,
the time will come
when he will have the courage to face you
and tell you what he truly feels for you.
And when the time is right,
he'll shout out to the world
how much he loves you.
But for now,
just let him secretly express his feelings
through secret messages.
It's a long story, but I was thinking,
the reason why you're sending me
your sweet secret messages is...
that... you have secret feelings for me.
I know... I know, I know, I know
so you don't have to look at me that way.
And besides, I know I'm not your type
especially when I saw
your ex-girlfriend Antonia.
There's a huge difference between us.
If you compare Antonia with me,
that's heaven and earth...
I'm the earth part...
That's heaven and earth.
You too, you're heaven.
Heaven, heaven, heaven.
That's you and Antonia.
You're both heaven while I'm the earth
and you really won't fall for me.
And besides,
how would you fall for your crude cook?
That's impossible and I know that.
Why would it be impossible?
You're not difficult to like.
But you're right.
You're not my type.
Anyway, thanks for your honesty, Florence.
Let's see each other in school tomorrow.
Thanks for listening
and for your understanding.
Goodnight.
He said I'm not difficult to like.
Oh my, I'm already late!
Why are you still here?
You'll be late.
No, Ms. Serafica, this won't take long.
I'll be finished soon.
Hey, Don Ferell and I talked already.
You just have to focus on your school.
I'll take care of the kitchen.
No, Ms. Serafica, I can do this.
I'm almost done.
I know you can do it,
but we want to help you
to lessen the pressure on you.
After all, you need to adjust
to your new school.
Go!
What are you waiting for? Go!
Thank you, Ms. Serafica.
Thank you.
What's with you, Florencia?
The first day, you were sent to the office.
Now you're late.
Good luck to your academic performance.
Hello, Lina.
I need your help.
Please see me in the AVP room.
AVP room?
Yes. Please, Florence.
Please come and see me now.
Okay, I'm on my way.
Hello, Lina, I'm here on the third floor.
Where are you?
Yes, just head inside the door, Florence.
I already saw the door. What's the problem?
Do you have a problem?
Hurry, please.
Lina, I'm already here in the AVP room.
Where are you?
[Audio Visual Room]
Lina? Lina!
Hey!
Is there someone there?
Open the door.
Hello?
Lina!
Lina, are you there?
This is so boring. There's no picture.
Guys.
Have you seen Florence?
No. Maybe she has a class.
I know she has a class right now.
But I passed by her classroom
and she was not there.
Yes, I haven't seen her today.
What happened to her?
I've been looking for her
for quite some time.
Is there someone there? Open the door.
Hello!
Hey, if you're joking,
this is not a good joke.
This is a bad joke.
Please open the door.
Hey, Lina!
You're not funny if you're joking.
Open the door.
Hello, is there someone there?
Hey, guys.
Relax, it's just me.
What do you need?
I'm just looking for Nero.
Have you seen him?
Oh, Nero.
He's just there.
Hey, where did he go?
Please!
Is anyone there?
Hello?
Is there anyone there? I got locked inside.
Kindly open the door.
Why is there no signal?
Hello!
I'm begging you, I'll be late for my class.
Lina!
Congrats...
You followed our instructions.
Finally, you're learning.
I'm begging you...
Florence!
Drink some more.
I'm okay now.
We have a clinic.
Do you want me to take you there?
I'm okay now.
Thank you for saving me earlier.
I thought I'd be locked there forever.
Are you sure
they didn't do anything else to you?
They just locked you inside the room?
Yes.
I just had a panic attack
because I'm scared of the dark.
That's really my biggest phobia
and what I hate most.
Maybe a traumatic event happened to you
when you were young.
Maybe, or I just get scared easily.
How did you find out where I was earlier?
Where is she?
If you won't tell me where she is,
you'll have to fight with me.
Camille and Aira won't stop bothering me.
Do you want us to report them to the dean?
No need.
So you'll just let them?
It's not that I'll just let them be.
But I just thought Lina will be blamed
because she's the one
who called me to go there.
That's how Camille and Aira work
by deniability.
I'm sure if I'll report them,
they'll just deny it and in the end,
Lina will be reprimanded by the dean.
She might even get suspended.
Even though in truth,
she was just used in this situation.
She's a victim...
A victim of Camille and Aira, just like me.
But still, she let them use her.
Nero, not everyone is as brave as you.
And not everyone can make a stand easily.
If you'll let this slide now,
for sure, they'll just repeat it.
Don't worry, I'll just be careful.
Extra, extra, more.
Just don't mind them.
You're really a good person, Florence.
I told you, you're not difficult to like.
For our pilot episode,
we'll talk about
the most important and special day
that is unique only for Gyronella University.
A day we like to call Agora Day.
Today is a very important day
because we will be deciding
who from the school committee
who will be working with me
in organizing our exciting activities.
All right then,
that makes Camille the head...
I object!
I nominate myself
to be the student representative
of the Communication Arts department.
For the first time
in the university's history,
there are two nominees
to be the representative
of the Communication Arts department.
What do you think, Aldus?
Who is your bet in this battle?
You know,
in the short time that I've known you,
your best quality is your heart.
There are a lot of intelligent and witty people
in this world.
But if only there are more people like you,
this world would be so different.
It'll be a whole lot better.
That's why don't doubt yourself.
Show everybody the power of your heart.